Finding Aid for the Stafford Leak Warren Papers LSC.0987
UCLA Library Special Collections
- III. Operation Crossroads Papers.
  - Assorted Graphs and Charts., 1945-46.; 36 items:
    - 4. Copy graph, probable surface and air areas of contamination 2 hours after explosion., undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 5. Graph, logarithmic plot of critical range (5100-5500A), by Ensign Walton, Liaison, Air Safety., (2pp. plus graph insert). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 6. Copy nautical chart, streamline current chart, Western Pacific Ocean,, Hydrographic Office, Washington D.C., May-September, November 1944. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 7. Folder, with time chart from Queen Day, SLW., undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 8. Copy natical chart, Marshall Islands Northern Portion (with Able Day chart on reverse), Hydrographic Office, Washington D.C.., June, October 1945. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 9. Transparency, scale for predicted exposure, first operation., undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 10. Copy diagram, radiological safety circuits, CJTF-One., June 21, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 11. Copy diagram, maximum hourly air transport over Eniwetok., August 1945. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 12. Copy diagram, maximum hourly air transport over Eniwetok., September 1945. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 13. Copy diagram, maximum hourly air transport over Eniwetok., October 1945. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 14. Copy diagrams, hourly air transport observed over Eniwetok., May 7, 14, 19, 22, 25, 31, 1945.; (6pp.). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 15. Copy diagrams, maximum hourly air displacement, Eniwetok., May-July 1945.; (cover note plus 3 diagrams). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 16. Copy diagram, surface winds, Eniwetok., May-October 1945.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 17. Copy graph, typical easterly winds., May, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 18. Copy graph, typical easterly winds., June, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 19. Copy graph, typical easterly winds., July, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 20. Copy graph, typical east-west winds., May, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 21. Copy graph, typical east-west winds., June, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 22. Copy graph, typical east-west winds., July, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 23. Copy graph, maximum recorded hourly northward and southward air displacement cross-section, Eniwetok., May 1945.; (2 pieces). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 24. Copy graph, maximum recorded hourly eastward and westward air displacement cross-section., May 1945.; (2 pieces). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 25. Copy graph, daily wind observations on Eniwetok., May 1945. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 26. Copy chart, size and characteristics of airborne solids, American Air Filter Company, Incorporated, Louisville, Kentucky., 1937. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 27. Copy chart, operational days based on Eniwetok., July-August 1945. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 28. Copy map, positions after 1 and 2-day periods of centers of radioactive clouds, originated at Bikini., May 1945.; 10,000 ft. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 29. Copy map, positions after 1 and 2-day periods of centers of radioactive clouds, originated at Bikini., May 1945.; 40,000 ft. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 30. Copy chart, percentage frequency of wind speed and direction classes at selected levels at Kwajalein., undated; (5pp.). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 31. Copy chart, percentage frequency of wind speed and direction classes at selected levels at Eniwetok., undated; (7pp.). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 32. Copy graph, wind for Eniwetok., May 1945.; (4 graphs). (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 33. Rough diagram, width of path of material from column., undated; 50,000 ft. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 34. Rough graph, distance traveled., May [no year]. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 35. Rough graph, distance traveled., undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 36. Rough diagram., undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Memos and Reports., March 1946.; 31 items:
    - 1. Copy memo, George M. Lyon to Rear Admiral H.W. Smith (MC) U.S. Navy., January 20, 1946.; (6pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 2. Copy report, radiological safety annex to safety plan page 1 missing)., February 4, 1946.; (13 of 14 pages; (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 3. Copy memo, G.M. Lyon for SLW to Commander Ashworth, U.S. Navy., February 6, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 4. Copy memo, Colonel Wiley D. Ganey, Air Corps to Captain Lyon, U.S. Navy., February 11, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 5. Copy memo, R.A. Sawyer to SLW and others., February 20, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 6. Copy memo, Lieutenant Colonel C. Vanden Bulck to General Nichols., February 23, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 7. Letter, John H. Lawrence, M.D. to SLW., February 26, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 8. Copy memo, 014 (G.M.Lyon) to 015., February 26, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 9. Copy memo, Rad. Safety 013 A (SLW) to Technical Director, Operation Crossroads., March 5, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 10. Copy memo, rough draft, The Chief of Bureau of Ships to Commander Western Sea Frontier., undated; (3pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 11. Copy memo, Colonel Paul C. Gilliland, (MC) O.A.S. to SLW., March 7, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 12. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to 00 via J-1., March 7, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 13. Copy memo, CJTF-One (W.H.P. Blandy) to Commanding General, Army Air Forces, Att: Army Air Surgeon., March 7, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 14. Copy memo, SLW to Rear Admiral Ross T. McIntyre., March 8, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 15. Copy memo, J-015 (G.M. Lyon) to J-1., March 12, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 16. Copy memo, J-015 (G.M. Lyon) to 0-1., March 12, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 17. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-1., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 18. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to C.G. Joint Task Group 1.5., March 15, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 19. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-1., March 15, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 20. Copy memo, 2nd Lieutenant L.E. Rasmussen, MAC to all concerned., March 19, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 21. Copy memo, SLW to Area Engineers, Berkeley, California., March 20, 1945. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 22. Copy list, personnel boarding U.S.S. Haven sailing Apr. 4, 1946, 013 E (SLW) to J-1., March 21, 1946.; (7pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 23. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-1., March 21, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 24. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-1., March 22, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 25. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to Chief of Naval Personnel., March 25, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 26. Copy memo, Radiological Safety Advisor (SLW) to the Commander Task Group 1.2., August 14, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 27. Copy memo, G.M. Lyon to Commander, Joint Task Force One., October 11, 1946.; (5pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 28. Copy table, radioactivity, U.S.S. Salt Lake City, Baker Test., undated; (5pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 29. Copy chart, radiological situation on target ships, Test Baker., undated; (9pp.). (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 30. Graph, target ship contamination., undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 31. Copy graph, target ship contamination., undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Notes, Memos and Reports., March-April 1946.; 52 items:
    - 1. Rough notes., March 2, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 2. Rough notes., undated; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 3. Letter, James H. Sterner, M.D., Kodak Company to SLW., March 5, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 4. Copy letter, SLW to Dr. Andrew H. Dowdy, University of Rochester., March 7, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 5. Copy report, public information estimate no.1, Fitzhugh Lee, Captain, U.S Navy., March 7, 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 6. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-4., March 7, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 7. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-4., March 7, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 8. Copy memo, 016 (Herbert Scoville, Jr. for SLW) to J-4., March 8, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 9. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-4., March 8, 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 10. Copy memo, SLW to JFT-One., March 8, 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 11. Copy list with notes, Manhattan District Engineer Officers., March 11, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 12. Copy list with notes, assigned Brooke General Hospital Temporary Duty., March 12 [no year]. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 13. Copy list, with notes, enlisted men assigned from AAF to CJTF-One., undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 14. Copy list, with notes, assigned from U.S.P.H.S.., April 4, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 15. List, summary of personnel, by Captain Birchard M. Brundage, M.C.., March 12, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 16. Copy memo, J. Shakenberg, Chief of Staff, to Division Heads and Officers preparing annexes to CJTF-1 operation plan no.1-46, rough draft., March 12, 1946.; (16pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 17. Copy operation plan, no.1-46, rough draft., March 12, 1946.; (16pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 18. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-4., March 12, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 19. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to J-4., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 20. Copy memo, 013 E (Birchard M. Brundage, Captain AUS) to J-20., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 21. Copy communication, CJTF-One to CG Oakland Army Base., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 22. Copy memo, CJTF-One (David H. Blakelock by direction) to Chief Supply Service, Office of the Surgeon General., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 23. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to Lieutenant Joe Barber, U.S.N.R.., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 24. Copy memo, 013 E (Birchard M. Brundage)., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 25. Memo, Commander J.K. Leydon to SLW., March 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 26. Copy memo, 013 E (A.A. de Lorimier, Colonel (M.C.) for SLW) to J-4., March 18, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 27. Copy memo, 013 E (Herbert Scoville, Jr. for SLW) to 00., March 18, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 28. Copy memo, 013 # (A.A. de Lorimier, Colonel (M.C.) for SLW) to J-33., March 18, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 29. Memo, J-015 (G.M. Lyon) to Captain Brundage, (M.C.) AUS., March 19, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 30. Copy memo, 013 E (Herbert Scoville, Jr. for SLW) to J-4., March 20, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 31. Copy letter, Lieutenant Colonel Todd to Colonel Large., March 20 [no year]. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 32. Copy memo 013 E (SLW) to J-4., March 20, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 33. Copy report, Performance Data on Victoreen Beta Gamma Counter, Model X-263, Russell S. Leone, Colonel (M.C.) to Chief Radiological Safety Section JTF-One, Att: G.M. Lyons., March 20, 1946.; (9pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 34. Copy report, Estimation of Hazard from Airborne Radioactive Material with Graphs, by Dr. Herbert Scoville, Jr., undated; (9pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 35. Graph, terminal velocity for drops of unit density., undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 36. Copy graph, terminal velocity for drops of unit density., undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 37. Table I, rate of fall and travel of drops of different sizes., undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 38. Copy memo, list of civilian personnel participating in JFT-One, Robert J. Buettner to Lieutenant Colonel C. Vanden Bulck., March 22, 1946.; (6pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 39. Copy memo, 013 E (Herbert Scoville, Jr. for SLW) to hydrographer., March 25, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 40. List, ship distances, Able Day., undated; (5pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 41. Confirmation, SLW to JTF-One., March 27, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 42. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to Technical Director., March 29, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 43. Copy ships location summary, JTF-One., March 29, 1946.; (7pp.). (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 44. Calendar., April-August [no year]. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 45. Report, Cockpit Background Radiation on F6F Navy Fighter, by Ensign Howard Walton, Jr., Liaison, Air Safety., April 5, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 46. Rough notes., April 5, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 47. List, personnel, Able., April 8, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 48. Rough list, personnel, Able and Baker., April 8, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 49. Copy list, voice calls, initial boarding teams communications., June 18, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 50. Copy list, voice calls, initial boarding teams communications., undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 51. Copy receipt of material, i.e. letter, SLW to DSM., August 15 [no year]. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 52. Rough notes., undated; (2). (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Memos, Letters, and Communications., April 1946.; 26 items:
    - 1. Manual, Staff Instructions, W.H.P. Blandy, Vice Adm., Washington: U.S. Printing Office., April 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 2. Copy selections from Staff Instructions, CJTF-One., April 1946.; (7pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 3. Copy list, with notes, Crossroads personnel., April 2, 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 4. Memo, 013 E (SLW) to Admiral Parsons., April 4, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 5. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to Admiral Parsons., April 4, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 6. Note, 013 E to Admiral Parsons., undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 7. Copy list, with notes, Crossroads personnel., April 2, 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 8. Memo, 013 (SLW) to Admiral Parsons., April 4, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 9. Copy memo, 013 (SLW) to Admiral Parsons., April 4, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 10. Note, SLW to Admiral Parsons., undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 11. Copy letter, George M. Lyon, Captain, to Mrs. Genevieve Mason., April 8, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 12. Copy memo, George S. Jackson to all group heads in DTFC for Technical., April 16, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 13. Notes, personnel, SLW., undated; (15pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 14. Copy memo, G.M. Lyon to Lieutenant David Green Doane., April 15, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 15. Copy memo, Hymer L. Friedell, Lieutenant Colonel Medical Corps to Deputy District Engineer, Manhattan District., April 16, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 16. Copy memo, Captain Fitzhugh Lee to SLW and others., April 18, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 17. Note, from H.S., undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 18. Copy telegram, CJTF-One to SLW., April 18, 1946.; (2 duplicates). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 19. Copy letter, from SLW., April 19, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 20. Memo routing slip., undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 21. Copy memo, Curtis A. Nelson, Lieutenant Col to Colonel E.E. Kirkpatrick., April 19, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 22. Copy memo, David H. Blake lock to Rad Safe, Att: SLW., April 19, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 23. Copy message, War Department SLW to CJTF-One., April 20, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 24. Copy memo, Herbert Scoville for SLW to J-4., April 27, 1946.; (2 duplicates). (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 25. Rough roster., March 29, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 26. Rough notes., May 8 [no year]. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Memos, Letters and Lists., May 1946.; 17 items:
    - 1. Copy memo, with graphs, J.O. Hirschfelder to W.S. Parsons., May 8, 1946.; (5pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 2. Copy telegram, Clarke, USEO to SLW., May 9, 1946.; (3 duplicates). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 3. Copy memo, SLW to Major General Groves., May 11, 1946.; (2 duplicates). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 4. Copy list, personnel., May 20, 1946.; (18pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 5. Copy memo, Robert J. Buettner to Colonel Herbert C. Gee., May 24, 1946.; (6pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 6. Copy list, Manhattan District personnel on duty with Operation Crossroads., undated; (2 duplicates, 6pp. each). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 7. Copy list, personnel, Oceanographic Section., undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 8. Copy memo, Robert J. Buettner to Commanding Officer, U.S. Engineer Office., May 28, 1946.; (5pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 9. Letter, Walton to SLW., May 28, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 10. Copy memo, Technical Director (R.A. Sawyer) to 013 E (SLW) and others., May 29, 1946.; (2pp. with 7 enclosures). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 11. Copy memo, CJTF-One (J.A. Snackenberg, Chief of Staff) to JTF-One., May 29, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 12. Copy memo, J.A. Snackenberg, Chief of Staff, to JTF-One Staff., May 30, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 13. Copy memo, J.E. Martin, Lieutenant U.S.N.R. to SLW., May 30, 1946.; (3pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 14. Copy memo, J.E. Martin Lieutenant U.S.N.R. to Chiefs of Sections, JTF #1, U.S.S. Haven., May 31, 1946.; (3pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 15. Copy instructions, Lagoon Patrol., undated; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 16. Memo, radiological air data., undated; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 17. Copy memo, radiological air data., undated; (2 duplicates, 4pp. each). (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Memos and Reports., June 1946.; 39 items:
    - 1. Copy memo, G.M. Lyon to Chief, Radiological Safety (SLW) and others., June 1, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 2. Copy memo, G.M. Lyon to Chief, Radiological Safety (SLW) and others., June 1, 1946.; (2 duplicates, 2pp. each). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 3. Copy memo, J-015 (G.M. Lyon) to J-1 Administration Unit., June 3, 1946.; (3pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 4. Copy memo, W.S. Parsons to J-3 (Air Ops.)., June 9, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 5. Copy memo, John W. Talbot, Lieutenant Colonel M.C., Chief Air Monitor., June 11, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 6. Copy memo, Deputy Task Force Commander for Technical Direction (W.S. Parsons) to Radiological Safety Advisor and others., June 12, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 7. Copy map, busy stations., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 8. Report, Danger from Suspended Radioactive Material in the Air, W.A. Kemper to SLW., June 13, 1946.; (6pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 9. Copy memo, John M. Talbot, Lieutenant Colonel to the Communications Officer, U.S.S. Haven., June 14, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 10. Memo, flying status for air monitors, enlisted, SLW to CJTF-One, Att: Chief of Staff, J-1., June 15, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 11. Memo, flying status for air monitors, commissioned, SLW to CJTF-One, Att: Chief of Staff, J-1., June 15, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 12. Copy memo, Wright H. Langham to Raemer Schreiber., June 15, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 13. Memo, James D.C. Breckenridge to Chief, Radiological Safety Section, U.S.S. Haven., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 14. Memo, James D.C. Breckenridge to Chief, Radiological Safety Section, U.S.S. Haven., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 15. Memo, J-015 (G.M. Lyon) to Chiefs of Sections, Technical Staff, U.S.S. Haven., June 17, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 16. Memo, J-015 (G.M. Lyon) to Chief, Radiological Safety Section., June 17, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 17. Copy memo, Electronics Coordinating Officer, JTF-1 (C.C. Ijams, by direction) to Commanding Officer, Coasters Harbor, Attn: Lieutenant Commander Van Osdol., June 19, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 18. Copy memo, Commander Task Unit 1.1.2 (A.C. Thorington) to Task Unit 1.1.2. and others., June 20, 1946.; (2 duplicates, 2pp. each). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 19. Copy memo, Technical Director (R.A. Sawyer) to CJTF-One., June 21, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 20. Memo, Officer in Charge of Destroyer Monitors (W.A. Wulfman) to Chief, Radiological Section., June 21, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 21. Copy memo, CJTF-One (R. Brodie, Jr. by direction) to distribution list., June 21, 1946.; (3pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 22. Appendix, draft, Security Directive Covering Results of A, and B, Operation Crossroads., undated; (3pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 23. Copy memo, Technical Director (R.A. Sawyer) to A11013 groups., June 25, 19461.; (3pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 24. Copy report, Radiological Danger Areas for Air Operations., June 27, 1964.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 25. Memo, Wiley D. Ganey, Colonel, to Radiological Safety Advisor., June 28, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 26. Copy memo, 013 E (SLW) to 013., June 28, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 27. Copy report, Program for Land Survey, Enyu, Bikini and Amen., June 28, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 28. Copy notes, Conference of Staff Division Heads,, D.R. Bergh, Flag Secretary., June 27, 1946, June 29, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 29. Copy instructions, for Surface Patrol (TG 1.7)., June 22, 1946.; (3 duplicates, 3pp. each). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 30. Rough notes, Newell., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 31. Calculations, Results of Conference on Plane Distances., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 32. Copy calculations, Results of Conference on Plane Distances., undated; (5 duplicates). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 33. Calculations, Results of Conference on Plane Distances, SLW., June 21, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 34. Rough notes, Basis for Judgement, distances., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 35. Report, Basis for Judgement, distances., undated; (1 original, 5 duplicates). (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 36. Chart, nuclear radiation protection chart, (Tests A and B)., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 37. List, Recommendations, Radiolo., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 38. Rough memo, Colonel Watrier to Colonel Gawy., undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 39. Graph, cloud technique, Dr. Newall., undated; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Assorted Memos and Lists., July 1946.; 16 items:
    - 1. Copy schedule, Operation TG 1.7, Edward N. Parker, Captain U.S. Navy., June 22, 1946.; (6pp.). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 2. Copy memo, CJTF-One (C.H. Lyman) to JTF-One., June 29, 1946.; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 3. Memo, Project Officer, Oceanographic Section (J.R. Lyman) to Chief, Radiological Safety Section., July 3, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 4. Copy memo CJTF-One (C.H. Lyman, by direction) to Distribution List., July 4, 1946.; (2 duplicates, 7pp. each). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 5. Report, Proposed Method of Plotting a Radioactive Area, by Lieutenant C.C. Waugh with cover note from A.A. de Lorimier., July 10, 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 6. Memo, Lieutenant C.C. Waugh to SLW., July 11, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 7. Note, to Colonel de Lorimier., July 13, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 8. Copy schedule, Operation TG 1.7., July 17, 1946.; (4pp.). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 9. Copy mailgram, CJTF-One to JTF-One., July 19, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 10. Copy instructions, signal operating, use of IFF, Alan D. Clark, Colonel, Air Corps Chief of Staff., July 20, 1946.; (5 duplicates). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 11. Copy roster, job assignments for Radiological Safety Section, Test Baker., July 21, 1946.; (6pp.). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 12. Copy list, job assignments, personnel in charge, Radiological Safety Section for Test Baker., July 21, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 13. Copy roster, final assignments, Radiological Safety Section, Test Baker., July 21, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 14. Copy list, personnel Radiological Safety Section, U.S.S. Haven., August 1, 1946.; (2 duplicates, 17pp. in first copy, 18pp. in second copy, p. 15 repeated). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 15. Copy list, JTF-One personnel., undated; (17pp.). (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 16. Copy memo form, Contractor's Representative, University of California to Dr. (Mr.) John Doe., undated; (2pp.). (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Sketch, List, Routing Slips and Regulations., September 1946.; 5 items:
    - 1. Copy sketch, H.J. Summers, Down for the Count., September 7, 1946. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - 2. List, personnel names and addresses, JTF-One., September 21, 1946.; (15pp.). (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - 3. Copy routing slip, Buettner to Dr. G. Dessauer., undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - 4. Copy routing slip, Buettner to SLW., undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - 5. Copy Radiological Safety Regulations, by SLW., undated; (5pp.). (Box 74, Folder 9)